新晋的
水晶
宝石
欢迎关注微博@ UUU字幕组 获取最新熟肉信息!
出品
UUU字幕组
翻译
考生D
校对
右翼部鸣明/ Husky
特效
presisco
压制
噢! 还是天然的沙踩起来自在
Oh! Good, old natural sand!
我实在消受不起动物园的高级沙
That fancy zoo sand was too fine for me.
嘿! 史蒂文!
Hey! Steven!
康妮!
Connie!
你们回来了! 而且平安无事!
You're back, and you're okay!
你去穿了耳洞呀?
Did you get your ears pierced?
你不会相信我们都遭遇了什么!
Oh, man, you're not gonna believe what happened!
我们去了遥远的太空站
We went to a far-off space station,
交了些新朋友 还扭曲了时空!
we made some new friends, we warped the space-time continuum!
没带你一起走真是抱歉
I'm sorry we left you behind.
没关系啦 你当时急着找回你爸
It's okay. You were really worried about your dad.
你们平安回来我就安心了
I'm just glad you're all back safe.
没错! 多亏了这个小家伙
Yep--all thanks to this guy.
我们不在的时候有出什么事吗?
Did anything happen while we were gone?
呃...狮子表现的很乖
Uh...Lion behaved himself,
我给家里买了麦片 还把毛巾通通洗了洗
I restocked all the cereal and washed all the towels.
听起来一切安好啊
Sounds like everything went well.
这个嘛 是有一个插曲啦...
Well, there was a little trouble...
接到你的电话时
When I got that call from you,
我就知道肯定发生了不少事情
I could tell you had a lot going on.
爸爸身陷困境
Dad's in trouble and we need
而且我们得前往太空将他带回来
to go into space to get him back!
我15分钟到
I can get there in 15.
不 也许20-25分钟 我可能要搭公车过去--
Or actually maybe 20, 25 'cause I might have to take the bus--
没时间了! 我们现在就得走
There's no time! We're going right now.
一定要在我们离开后保护好沙滩市!
Just protect Beach City for me while we're gone!
放心交给我吧!
You can count on me!
这不是只身能轻松挑起的担子
It was a big job for one person,
但我乐于接受挑战
but I felt up to the challenge.
当我抵达你家时
I made my way over to your house,
进门的那一刻便发现...
and that's when I realized...
里头有不速之客
I wasn't alone.
喝!
Hyah!
你都不敲门的吗?
Uh, don't you knock?
没礼貌
Weirdo.
橄榄石? 青金石?
Lapis? Peridot?
你们在厕所干嘛?
What are you doing here?
炫耀我的旧居给我--
Just showing off my old room to--
不 等等
Oh, wait.
我们做什么关你什么事!
Actually, that's none of your business!
她是谁? 为什么会在史蒂文家里?
Who is this, and what is she doing in Steven's house?
她是史蒂文第三要好的朋友 排在我和你后面
That's Steven's third-best friend after me and you.
呃 青金石 你不记得我了吗?
Um, Lapis, you don't remember me?
嗯...
Mmm...
那次你打算偷走全世界的水
You almost drowned me
差点把我淹死
when you tried to steal the world's water.
我差点淹死的人太多了
I almost drowned a lot of people.
我是康妮
I'm Connie.
我是橄榄石! 然后这是我们的南瓜
I'm Peridot! And this is our pumpkin.
噢! 你好!
Oh! Hello!
史蒂芬跟我说你们在乡下休养
So Steven told me you guys retired to the country.
怎么突然跑到这儿来了?
What brings you here?
石榴交给我们了个任务!
Garnet trusted us with a mission!
史蒂文也托付了任务给我呢
Oh, Steven gave me one, too.
但愿我不会让他失望
I just hope I don't let him down.
十之八九会吧
You probably will.
所以水晶宝石们才要我们来负责守卫沙滩市
That's why they put us in charge of protecting Beach City.
但那也是史蒂文要我做的!
But Steven asked me to do that!
你真的觉得你帮得上忙?
You really think we need your help?
等一下!
Wait a minute!
我们搞不好真需要你帮忙
Maybe we do need your help.
水晶宝石以前都是组成特定队形
The crystal gems have been protecting this world
来守护地球
with a specialized team.
三个宝石人各司其职 再加上一个人类!
Three gems, each with their own role, and a human!
呃 史蒂芬只算半个人类 不过 差不多啦
Well, Steven's only half human, but, hmm, close enough.
所以?
Meaning?
想要做水晶宝石队
To do the job of the crystal gems,
必须成为水晶宝石队!
we need to do the jobs of the crystal gems!
-我们四个---四个?
-We four---Four?
南瓜也算
I'm counting Pumpkin.
我们都要挑一个水晶宝石
We each need to pick someone from the original team
扮演她们在队伍里的角色!
and perform their role in the group!
青虽出于蓝--但更胜于蓝!
We can be exactly like them--but better!
感觉...有点道理
That sort of makes sense.
我选石榴!
I call Garnet!
显然我最适合扮演指挥的角色
I'm obviously best suited to being the boss.
你是满有领导气质的
You are very bossy.
谢谢夸奖
Thank you.
那么我延续史蒂文的精神
Then I'll do what Steven does.
青金石 你可以当紫晶
Lapis, you can be Amethyst.
哪个是紫晶? 开玩笑啦
Which one is she? I'm joking.
很好! 你已经进入角色了!
Great!-You're already in character!
那你们的南瓜呢?
What about your pumpkin?
随便 当她是珍珠吧
Whatever. She can be Pearl.
新水晶宝石队! 集合!
New crystal gems, congregate!
我的意思是要你们靠过来摆个酷炫的姿势
That means come over here and do a cool pose.
嗯...
Hmm!
我看看...
Let's see...
没有异常...
Nothing there.
比照史蒂文的描述 市内一切正常!
Judging from what Steven tells me, everything's normal!
你们快说说
There! Am I doing it?
我有没有表现出石榴不凡的高冷气质?
Am I as aloof and distant as the Garnet?
有啊 只是张嘴发问就破功了!
You were, until you started to ask so many questions!
来人帮忙啊
Help!
听起来是从洗车店传来的!
That sounds like it's coming from the car wash!
出动! 新水晶宝石队!
Go! New crystal gems!
沙滩市民 汝因何呼救
What seems to be the trouble here, Beach City citizen?
救救我爸!
It's my dad!
有混混老是找他脑袋的麻烦!
Some jerks have been messing with his head!
一开始满好笑的...
It was funny...
但是逼我来处理就不好笑了
till he made me bring it here.
你们可以洗掉吧?
Can you guys wash it off?
对喔!
Oh, right!
既然宇宙父子还在外太空...
If Mr. Universe and Steven are in outer space then...
只能由我们经营洗车店了!
we should run the car wash!
咳咳
Ahem.
呃 那我们赶紧动"水"吧?
Uh, "water"we waiting for?
唉呦史蒂文 不错喔
Ha ha! Good one, Steven.
随你怎么说吧 老兄
Whatever you say, dudes. Burp!
说得很好 珍珠
Well said, Pearl!
什么? 哇!
What? Whoa!
您的爱车--已洗净擦干!
Here's your vehicle--washed and buffed!
由新水晶宝石队技术提供!
Courtesy of the new crystal gems!
刚刚超酷的
That was cool.
谢谢光临!
Thanks!
经过折腾与磨合
After such a rocky start,
新水晶宝石队总算
it finally seemed like the new crystal gems
有了搭档的默契
were coming together!
又或只是巧合?
Or were we?
哇!
Whoa!
看来我们的口碑已经传开了
Looks like word got around.
再秀一手! 再秀一手!
Encore! Encore!
我知道大家聚集在这里的真正目的!
I know what everyone is really here to see!
沙滩市民 准备见证 唯一的石榴!
Beach City citizens, witness the Garnet!
紫晶 你要出戏了啦!
Amethyst,-your performance is lacking!
你的搞笑属性呢!
Mess around!
来点段子啊!
Crack some jokes!
噢 我应该来点段子是吧?
Oh, is that what I'm supposed to be doing?
青金石! 呃 史蒂文我不觉得这有趣
Lapis! Uh, the Steven doesn't think that's funny!
哈
Ha.
我简直不敢相信!
I can't believe this! The only one taking
唯一扮演好份内的居然是南瓜!
anything seriously around here is Pumpkin!
就是这样 珍珠确实喜欢肥皂
That's right. Pearl does like soap.
那个 你们能不能把我们的车放下来?
Uh, hey, you gonna bring our car down?
不准干扰唯一的石榴!
Do not interrupt the Garnet!
都别急 给我一个一个来!
Everyone will have a turn!
糟糕!
Oops!
橄榄石! 放他下来!
Peridot, put that guy down!
没有任何人可以命令唯一的石榴!
No one bosses the Garnet!
石榴才不会对人大喊大叫!
Well, Garnet wouldn't yell at people!
同意
I agree.
也许该换人扮演唯一的石榴了
Maybe you should let someone else play the Garnet.
诶?
Eh?
不!
No!
紫晶! 谁戴眼镜谁是石榴!
Amethyst, I have the glasses!
没有紫晶了
There is no Amethyst!
现在只有石榴!
Only Garnet!
你们到底在干嘛!
What are you guys doing?!
不好了...
Oh, no.
我必须史蒂文起来才行
Gotta Steven this somehow.
看看我们!
Look at us!
居然在彼此争斗!
We're all fighting with each other!
但我们彼此相爱
But we all love each other.
而你们都爱我
And you all love me.
所以我们要共同克服困难--
So we all have to do this together--
以爱的名义!
for love!
史蒂文的嘴炮应该要更有力道
Steven would have had a better speech.
就是嘛 没哭没深度
I know. She didn't even cry.
随着洗车场招牌的损毁
The wash was a wash.
新水晶宝石队同时分崩离析
And so were the new crystal gems.
我仔细分析了一下
I've done a lot of thinking
队伍出矛盾的原因
about what's been going wrong with this team-up,
我发现问题显然出在你们身上!
and I think it's obvious now that the problem is all of you!
康妮 你没有半点史蒂文多愁善感的特质
Connie, you completely lack Steven's sentimentality.
如果是他 昨天的演说肯定更加激励人心
He would have had a much more inspiring speech yesterday.
青金石 你欠缺幽默感 重挫团体士气
Lapis, your lack of humor has been hurting our morale.
干脆让你跟南瓜的角色互换好了
Maybe you should switch with Pumpkin.
让南瓜当石榴 你当珍珠
Let's make Pumpkin the Garnet. You should be the Pearl.
我跟珍珠哪里像了!
I'm nothing like Pearl.
她又神经紧绷还敏感兮兮的!
She's so uptight and sensitive!
你竟敢这么说我! 我要走了!
How dare you?! I'm leaving!
好好笑喔! 你才应该扮演紫晶!
That's so funny! You should be Amethyst!
蠢话连篇! 让你当野蛮人正好!
That's so dumb! You should be a clod!
哦 我现在又是野蛮人了? 我觉得你比较像
Oh, so now I'm a clod? I think you're the clod.
哇! 你连模仿橄榄石都模仿得这么糟!
Wow! Your Peridot impression is lousy, too!
你们都闭嘴可以吗!
Will you two can it?!
史蒂文才不会这样说话
That's not a very Steven thing to say.
那又怎样!
I don't care!
不像史蒂文就不像!
So I'm not Steven!
他或许确实很擅长劝架!
Maybe he's really great at helping people work out these arguments!
或许既有耐心又有爱心
Maybe he's really patient and caring,
还得强迫自己长大去面对你们这群超能力儿童
even though it must be hard for him having to be
这有多累人你们想过吗!
the adult for a bunch of super-powered children!
我们都比你们大上好几千岁
We're both thousands of years older than you.
那就表现得成熟点!
Then act like it!
表现像个历经淬炼的宝石人
Be the gems you've been for thousands of years,
停止幼稚的游戏吧
instead of playing this silly game.
光是模彷别人
It's impossible trying to solve problems
是不可能解决问题的!
if we're just trying to copy other people.
噢 这场闹剧有什么意义?
Oh, what's the point of this?
我们永远不会是水晶宝石队 顶多是...
We'll never be the crystal gems, we're just...
水品玉石队
the crystal temps.
但我们有我们自己办事的作风
But we have our own way of doing things.
让我们做回原来的自己 修正自己造成的错误
So let's go back to that, to fix this mess we made.
你现在的确有史蒂文的风范
You do make a good Steven.
注意言辞
Watch it.
好吧...
Well...
要说橄榄石擅长什么
if there's one thing Peridots are good at,
那就是修理东西!
it's fixing things!
我应该可以帮忙冲掉瓦砾
I guess I could help wash away the rubble.
我来整理团队进度
And I'll help us organize.
那么我们的第一步就从...
So here's how I think we should start...
你说你们破坏了洗车店?
You sure you wrecked anything?
没看出任何异状呀
The car wash looks good as new.
我们都修复了 除了招牌我们无能为力
Well, except, we couldn't repair the sign.
也是时候换招牌了
Well, about time I got a new one.
该打电话问候霓虹灯厂家啦
Guess I'll give my neon guy a call.
等等 先别急着掏腰包
Well, don't get out your checkbook yet.
带出来吧!
Bring it on out!
为您呈现...
Introducing...
全新招牌!
a new sign!
完美商用!
For your business!
手工打造!
We made it ourselves!
看起来超棒的对吧!
Look at it, it's great!
我...爱死了!
I think I love it!
真的吗!
Really?
旧招牌普普通通 但这块招牌拥有灵魂!
That old sign was okay, but this one's got personality!
虽然过程进行的有些差强人意
Well, it wasn't much of a mission,
但我们也协力完成了任务
but I guess we handled that all right.
我就知道你们可以的
I knew you would.
那我们可以摆胜利姿势了吗?
Does that mean we can do a victory pose?
好吧
Okay.
出动! 水品玉石队!
Together: Go, crystal temps!